knitpicks.com 2008-05-27

# Knit Picks Customer Service » Privacy Policy

Knit Picks is committed to safeguarding your privacy. Please read the following policy  
to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of  
our Web site and purchase through our catalogs. This policy may change from time to  
time so please check back periodically. 

Knit Picks and the KnitPicks.com collect information in several ways from its customers  
and users. Some personal information is gathered when you “proceed to check out” including  
but not limited to your name, physical mailing address, physical shipping address  
(if different than your mailing address), your email address, daytime telephone number,  
credit card number and expiration date and information about where you first learned  
about this site. In addition, to check out information we may ask you for personal  
information at other times.  Knit Picks and KnitPicks.com also occasionally ask  
users to complete surveys that are used for research purposes. 

When you visit the KnitPicks.com web site you are sharing any information you provide  
solely with Knit Picks and its corporate parent Crafts Americana Group, Inc. We maintain  
our own secure servers on our own premises and only our own employees have access  
to them. We use the information we collect from you to better serve your needs. From  
time to time we will send you advertising information about our products and services  
that we feel may be of interest to you. We deliver this information to you both via  
the US Post Office and through the Internet. When you place an order with our company  
or register for our weekly drawing, we assume you would not mind receiving additional  
offers from our company both in the mail and online. If you wish to be removed from  
either our postal mailing address list or our e-mail address list you can contact  
us via e-mail at CustomerService@KnitPicks.com or call us at (800) 574-1323 (U.S.  
and Canada), Monday through Friday 5:00 AM - 6:00 PM PT or Saturday 6:00 AM - 5:00  
PM PT. Outside the U.S. and Canada you can reach us at (360) 260-8900 x105 Monday  
through Friday 9:00 AM to 4:30 PM PT. Or feel free to write us at Knit Picks, PO Box  
870760 Vancouver Wa 98684-7760. 

In addition, we occasionally are asked by other responsible companies who market products  
similar to ours to share our customers’ personal information with them. We believe  
that sharing our knowledge is beneficial to both our company and our customers. Our  
customers benefit by receiving the broadest offering of crafting products possible  
at no additional charge. It also helps us build a mailing list of only those individuals  
who want to receive our catalogs. We have found that most of our customers enjoy getting  
a reasonable quantity of mail-order offers for craft products and magazines. When  
you place an order with KnitPicks.com, we will ask you to specify your preference  
regarding sharing your personal information with other companies. If you do not wish  
to receive these offers, we will not share your name with other companies. 

Finally, Knit Picks and KnitPicks.com may also disclose account information in special  
cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary  
to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our  
Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally  
or unintentionally) our rights or property, or the rights and property of anyone else  
that could be harmed by such activities. Knit Picks and KnitPicks.com may disclose  
or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires  
it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service,  
and improve our products and services. In addition, as we continue to develop our  
business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information  
generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the unlikely event that Knit  
Picks, KnitPicks.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information  
will of course be one of the transferred assets.
